Preliminary Guide to the Luther Brady papers, MS2147.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- UP0012 (Box 12)
  - 5th Int'l Mtg. on Progress in Radio-Onc. JCRO/OGRO5, Salzburg, Austria 5/10-14/95 (D. Kogelnik, 4/12/1995; "Biological Response Modifiers" M. Dzeda/L Snelling; "Contemp. Indic. for IORT" - Costleigh/Asrari/Ostapoviz/Mic./LWB; "The Present and Future Role for Monoclonal Antibodies in the Management of Cancer" - 4/14/95, LWB, C. Miyamoto, L. Snelling, J. Enrich, R. Class, March 1995 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - "Innovations in Brachytherapy in Gynecologic Onc." - ACS Nat'l Conf. on Gyn. Cancers, 4/6-8/95, Washington D.C. for CA journal to be published July/August 1995, March 6-8, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Radiation Oncology: Historical Development in Germany, by H.P. Heilmann, Prof., July 1995 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - "Treatment Related Complications of the Management of Carcinoma of the Prostate: A Review," by Costleigh/Longton, Hill, LWB; Chapter 19, Springer, November 1995 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "Trtmt of metastatic carcinoma of the prostate," Hans Goethuys, Luc Baert, H. VanPoppel, G. Lieskovsky, LWB, Z. Petrovich (AJCO 12/95), December 1995 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Intracavitary Brachytherapy for Carcinoma of the Esophagus: Seminars in Surgical Oncology-Brachytherapy Supplement, Micaily B, Miyamoto C, Freire Je, Brady LW, September 1996 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "High grade gliomas of the brain: I-125-EGFr as an adjuvant to primary tumors. Utilizations of the radiolabeled MAb 425/EMD 55900 in the management of high grade gliomas: - paper to be done end '93--RIT Mtg., Stuttgart, 10/92, Prof. Wannenmacher/Heiner Bihl MD/PhD, Katharinenhospital, Univ. Tubingen, Klinik fur Nuclearmedizin, October 1992 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - [Unlabeled], undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - "Radiation Oncology: Where Are We Going, Where Have We been?" Investigation Rad., Aug. '94, J.B. Lipppincott, August 1994 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- UP0013 (Box 13)
  - The Present and Future Role of Monoclonal Antibodies in the Management of Cancer--Summary, LWB (Dr. Vaeth's San Francisco Symposium), February 7, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "Radiotherapy & Skeletal Disorders" Bertoli & Brady for Murray Book, June 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Medicine article for Nov. 1988, LWB, November 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Innovative Techniques in Radiation Onc.: Clin. Research Programs to Improve Local & Regional Control in Cancer: LWB for ACS, 12/7-9/88, Los Angeles, CA, December 7-9, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Selective Chromosomal Damage and Cytotoxicity of I-125 Labeled Monoclonal Antibody 17-1A in Human Cancer Cells12" by D. Woo/D. Li (to be submitted-Jour. Nat'l Acad. Sciences", October 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Clin. Implications of Immunologic Phenotyping in Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma," Vonderheid, Tan, Sobel, Schwab, Micaily, Jegasothy (submitted to J. Am. Acad. Dermatol, 1986) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - When Should Node Negative Breast Cancer Patients Receive Adjuvant Treatment?, LWB, S.A. Fisher, 1/89, Editorial for T-ROC, January 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Accelerated Fractionation Rad Ther for Liver Mets Selection of an Optimal Patient Population for the Evaluation of Late Hepatic Injury" 1/89 IJRO Biol & Physics, Steve Leibel/Guse/Order/LWB et al, January 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Monoclonal Antibodies in the Trtmt of Metastatic Carcinoma to the Liver: Report of a Pilot Study Including Leukopheresis," Amendola, LWB, Woo, Markoe, et al, May 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Controversies in Bladder Cancer Management" --Editorial for Dr. Joel Nass by LWB & Frank Lamm, March 10, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "The Radiation Therapy of Early Stage Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma: The HU Experience--by B. Micaily, C. Moser,E. Vonderheid, C. Koprowski, D. Lightfoot, A. Markoe, LWB (to be Published), 9/89, September 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - RTOG -- "A Randomized Phase III Protocol for the Evaluation of Misonidazole with Radiation in the Treatment of Patients with Brain Metastasis (RTOG 7916)", September 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - RTOG--"A Limited Participation Phage I/II Randomized Prospective Clin. Trial for Hepatic Mets from Colorectal Ca Refractory to Chemo Comparing 125Iodine-Radiolabeled Mab 17-1A Ther. to Placebo Ther. by LWB, Markoe, Amendola, about 12/89, December 1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Total Skin Electron Beam and Total Nodal Irradiation of Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma: An Update of the Experience at HU," B. Micaily, O. Campbel, C. Moser, E. Vonderheid, LWB, Submitted to IJRO 12/89?, December 1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "The Radiotherapy of Ocular Disease," - AM Markoe, LWB< U Karlsson, J Shields, J Augsburger (1/17/90) Principles o& Practice of Radiation Oncology, January 17, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - RTOG LUng Thymosin Study (RTOG 83-21) (to be submitted to IJRO - 1/90), January 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - T-ROC - "NIH Consensus Develop. Conf. Statement on the Trtmt. of Early Stage Breast Ca," Odette Campbell (10/90?), October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - T-ROC - "Colorectal Ca & the Role for Leevamisole as Adjuvant Ther.," O. Campbell, MD, Fall 1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "Treatment of Malignant Gliomas with I-125 Labeled MAB against EGFR: A Phase I Study," D. Woo, A. Markoe, S. Dadparvar, Karlsson, Rackover, Peyster, Emrich, Teplewski, H. Koprowski, 4/11/90, Dr. Order's Journal: Antibody Immunoconjugates and Radiopharmaceuticals, April 11, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - "Malignant Astrocytomas Treated with I-125 Labeled MAD 425 Against EGFr: A Phase II Trial (7/91) LWB, Miyamoto, etc, July 1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Malignant Astrocytomas Treated with I-125 Labeled Antibody Against EGFr: A Phase I/II Trials," LWB, Rackover, Miyamoto, etc., July 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - "I-125 labeled anti-epidermal growth factor receptor-425 in the treatment of malignant astrocytomas-a pliot study," LWB, Markoe, Woo, Rackover, Koprowski, etc. J. Neurosurgical Sciences, 1/91, January 1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - "Malignant Asstrocytomas Treated with I-125 Labeled Monoclonal Antibody Against Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor: A Phase I/II Trial" sent to IJRO, 12/26/90, Miyamoto, LWB, Woo, Rackover, Emrich, etc., December 26, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - "Gynecologic Oncology" - Advances in Oncology journal (Bristol-Myers Onc. Div., Cliggott Communications (5/91), LWB/J. Dragun, May 1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - "Clinical Trials in Patients with High Grade Gliomas of the Brain" - LWB, Micaily, Hernandez, Miyamoto-Vaeth Lectureship, 2/21/91, San Francisoco, CA (10/91), February 21, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - "Tumors of the Retina Management of Retreatment of Retinoblastoma Failures," LWB, Hernandez, J. Shields, Amendola, September 1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - "Plaque Brachytherapy in the Treatment of Retinoblastoma," Hernandez, LWB, Shields, Shields, Amendola (12/6/91) to Robt. H. Sagerman, M.D., December 6, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Levitt & Tapley's TECHNOLOGICAL BASIS OF RADIATION THERAPY, 2nd Ed., S. Levitt, F. Khan, R. Potish, Lea & Febiger, 1992-Dr. B., chapter on eye tumors. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - "Lymphoid Tumors of the Orbit," M. Lambo, LWB< C.L. Shields (1/24/92) for R. Sagerman/Alberti (Springer-Verlag), January 24, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Cancer Cure with Organ Preservation Using Radiation Therapy - Summary"--Frontiers of Rad. Ther. & Onc. for 2/92 Mtg (John Meyer MD), LWB/G. Mieszkalski, February 1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Oncology Times "Mab-Guided Radioisotope Dramatically Improves Survival in Malignant Gliomas" - LWB/Miyamoto, March 30, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - "Five Year Experience with Interstitial Thermal Rad. Ther.: Part 2-Pelvic Tumors" H. Seegenschmiedt, Sauer, Miyamoto, Chala, LWB, RADIOLOGY, 3/92, March 1992 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "Radiotherapy of Ocular Malignancies" LWB/C. Hernandez; Editors Dr. Tobias/Prof. Thomas-Edward Arnold, Publishers, December 1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Radiation Therapy in the Treatment of Pituitary Adenomas - Salinger D, Brady LW, Miyamoto C. AmJ ClinOnCo 15 (6): 467-473, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - "Cost Accounting in Rad. Onc.: A Computer-Based Model for Reimbursement" 4/28/92, C.A. Perez, B. Kobeissi, etc, IJRO Biol. Phys., April 28, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - "New Advances in Radiation Onc. for Gynecologic Cancer," ACS Gyn. Conf., 4/2-4/92, Orlando, Fl., - LWB, Rotman, Calvo for consid. in CANCER (7/28/92), July 28, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - A Phase II Study of Murine Anti GD2/GD3 Monoclonal Antibody in the Ther. of Pts. with Dissem. Malig. Melanoma 5/15/88, Wistar Inst., Guerry, etc., May 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - "A Phase II Study of Murine Anti GD2/GD3 MAD in Ther. of Pts. with High Risk Choroidal Melanoma," LWB, Steplewski, Calvo, Hernandez, Shields, August 18, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Plaque Radiotherapy of Retinoblastoma, C Shields, Shields, ePotter, Hernandez, Brady, submitted: 1993 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Lymphoid Tumors of the Orbit, Chpter 23, M. Lambo, LWB, & Carol L. Shields, Springer-Verlag Publishers, 2/93, February 1993 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - "Metastatic Cancer Involving the Eye Manu." For R. Kagan MD 3/3/93 - Book, March 3, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - "Organ Preservation: Choroidal Melanoma treated by Brachytherapy" - LWB, Shields, Glennons, Hernandez (John Meyers, Front. Rad. Onc. 2/92 - sent 7/92), February 1992 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- UP0014 (Box 14)
  - PPR04 Chapter 29: Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma-- Bushil Beriwal (10/18/02 - Mr. Stander), 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - PPR04 Chapter 28-- Brain, Brain Stem & Cerebellum, -Dr. Loubna Scally, Chi Lin, S. Beriwal, 09/12/2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Kidney by Jeff M. Michakski, M.D. Rad. Onc., Mallinckrodt Inst. of Rad., St. Louis, MO - Wash. Univ. Sch. of Med., undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 15: 10RT (Intraoperative Radiation Therapy) Word by Calvo, F.A., Meirino, Gunderson/Willet - PPRO-4, To Mike Standen, 06/18/2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Laramore/Dr. M. Phillips Chapt. 21 "Particle Beam Radiother.: Clin. Perspective" for PPRO-4, 01/03/2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 22: Radioimmunoglobulins in Cancer Therapy (PPRO-4) by Drs. R. Class, C. Miyamoto, LWB, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 26- Skin by Dr. M. Solan, (PPRO-4) recv'd by Mr. Standen LWB, 02/13/2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 28: "Brain, Brain Stem and Cerebellum in Adults" by Dr. Curtis Miyamoto (PPRO-4), undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 32: Eye and Orbit, PPRO-4 by Drs. JE Freire, LWB, JA Shields, CL Shields, 03/08/2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 45: "Mediastinum & Trachea," PPRO-4 by Drs. Thomas, Emg & Scarbrough LB, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 46: "Esophagus" by Dr. Albert S. De Nittis (PPRO-4), 12/06/2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 48: Heart and Blood Vessels by Drs. Mark A. Chidel & Roger M. Macklis (PPRO-4), 10/19/2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 58: Bladder by Drs. Petrovish, J. Stein, G. Jozsef, S. Formenti, 02/12/2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 63: Endrometrium by Drs. Glassburn/LWB/P.W. Drigsby (PPRO-4), 10/19/2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 64: Ovary (PPRO-4) by Michael D. Stambaugh, M.D., 12/28/2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 65: Fallopian Tube by Drs. P. Guerrieri & LWB (PPRO-4), 12/06/2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 69: Adrenal Gland, PPRO-4 by Dr. Patrizia Guerrieri, 11/08/2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 73: "Bone" by P. Montemaggi, LWB, & Stephen M. Horowitz (PPRO-4), 11/08/2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 85: Radiation Treatment of Benign Disease (PPRO-4) Drs. W. Serber, LWB, M. Zhang, R.Hoppe, 02/12/2002 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- UP0015 (Box 15)
  Scope and Contents
  Reprints of articles authored by Luther W. Brady. No folders.
- UP0016 (Box 16)
  Invitations, programs, and summaries of medical conferences and meetings.
  - Northeast Regional Cancer Institute 9/8/97 Executive Committee Mtg., 09/08/1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Radiological Society Mtg. 5/17/97, Hershey Hotel, Hershey, PA, 05/17/1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Fraud and Abuse: Compliance and Integrity Programs," Presentation to ACRO by Gadi Weinreich, Esq., April 26, 1997, 04/26/1997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Daytona Beach, FL - 4/18-20/97, 04/18/1997 - 04/20/1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Advisory Board Company, The Medical Leadership Council-Great Physician Enterprise, 4/11-12/97, Pierre, 04/11/1997 - 04/12/1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fund 4/7/97 Cocktail Party, 6-8 p.m., 04/07/1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - American Brain Tumor Association Town Hall Mtg., 4/6/97, Holiday Inn Express, 1305 Walnut St., Phila., PA, 04/06/1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Four Seasons, 6/13/97 - Tasting, 06/13/1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - CANCER Editorial Advisory Board Mtg., Waldorf Astoria Hotel, NY, NY, 7/24/97 (Robert V.P. Hutter, MD), 07/24/1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Innovative Options in Rectal Cancer Management Mtg., Four Seasons Hotel, 5/19-20/97, Philadelphia, PA (G. Marks), 05/19/1997 - 05/19/1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - International Arts-Medicine Assn. Board Mtg., College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 6/14/97, 06/14/1997 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Allegheny Univ. Faculty Meetings 2/26/97, 6/25/97 (location to be announced) (Leonard L. Ross, Ph.D., Provost), 02/26/1997 - 06/25/1997 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- UP0017 (Box 17)
  - RSNA Ad Hoc Committee on Safety of Medical Uses of Low-Level Radiation, 5/25/94, O'Hare Hilton, Chicago, IL, 05/25/1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - RSNA Oral-History Project Interview, 5/24/94 (Stuart J. Birkby) at Four Seasons, 05/24/1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SCAROP Annual Mtg., Dallas/Ft. Worth, TX, 5/21-22/94 (Hyatt Regency Hotel), 05/21/1994 - 05/22/1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Phila. OB/GYN Review Course, 5/19/94, 8:30-9:00 am, Twelve Ceasars, 4200 City Line Ave. (Jeffrey S. Levy, MD), 05/19/1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - CME Course, Univ. of Minnesota, 5/11-13/94, Minneapolis, MN (Drs. Roger Potish/Seymour Levitt), 05/11/1994 - 05/13/1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Univ. of Alabama at Birmingham "Mock" On-Site Visit, 5/10/94, Birmingham, AL (Albert F. LoBuglio, MD), 05/10/1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - West Michigan Cancer Center, Kalamazoo, MI (Terry McKay), 5/4-5/94, 05/04/1994 - 05/05/1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - American Radium Society Annual Mtg., 4/22-26/94, Bermuda (Southampton Princess), 04/22/1994 - 04/26/1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Healthcare, 4/11/94, Blue Bell, PA (Lawrence Solin, MD), 04/11/1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Councilman Joseph C. Vignola, 4/7/94, City Hall, Room 404, 4th Fl., 4:00 p.m., 04/07/1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Blue Shield Annual Mtg., 4/6/94, Hershey Lodge & Convention Ctr., Nigerian Rm. (Walter Froh), 04/06/1994 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Villanova University Art Gallery, 3/27/94, 4:30 p.m. (Mary Anne Bartley, Brother Richard Cannuli, Director), 03/27/1994 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 3rd Annual Dosimetry/Physics Course 3/17-20/94, by HU at Wyndham Franklin Plaza Hotel, 03/17/1994 - 03/20/1994 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Review at Johns Hopkins, Baltimore, MD, 3/17/94 (Dr. Mary Bell), 03/17/1994 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Methodist Hospital, Brooklyn, NY, 3/16/94 - Visiting Professor (Mounzer Tchlebi, M.D.), 03/16/1994 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Blue Shield Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 3/2/94, 9 am. Camp Hill, PA, 03/02/1994 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - CANCER Journal Editorial Advisory Bd. Mtg., 3/1/94, Marriott Marquis Hotel, Atlanta, GA (Robt. V.P. Hutter, MD), 03/01/1994 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Univ. of Maryland - Visiting Professor 2/23/94, Baltimore, MD (Mohan Suntharalingam, MD/Omar Salazar, MD), 02/23/1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Society of Gynecologic Oncologists Mtg. 2/6-9/94, Hyatt Regency Grand Cypress, Orlando, FL, 02/06/1994 - 02/09/1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - CIGNA's pre-Academy Ball Reception 1/29/94, 5:30-7 pm, Academy of Music Rehearsal Hall (admission card req'd), 01/29/1994 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Samuel S. Fleisher Art Memorial -- Special Board Retreat, 1/22/94, 9:30am, Rohm and Haas, 6th & Market Sts., 01/22/1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Self Memorial Hospital Foundation, 1/20/94, Greenwood, SC (Anne Magruder), 01/20/1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Special Conference for UCLA, 1/15/94, Ritz Carlton Hotel, Rancho Mirage, CA (Robert G. Parker, M.D.), 01/15/1994 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Living Beyond Breast Cancer: "Tamoxifer..." Symposium, 11/13/93 (Marisa Weiss), 11/13/1993 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - ACS Clinical Advisory Group on Clin. Awards, 1/6-7/94, Atlanta, GA, 01/06/1994 - 01/07/1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - ACS Second National Conference on New Oncologic Agents: Practical Applications, 2/4-6/93, San Diego, CA, 02/04/1993 - 02/06/1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - MAB CHICAGO EXPENSES, 12/08/1990 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Second International Conference on Monoclonal Antibodies, 4/26-28/90, Naples, Italy, 04/26/1990 - 04/28/1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Huntsville, AL, 11/18/87 (Dr. Williams), 11/18/1987 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- UP0018 (Box 18)
  - Breast Cancer Conference 1996: Latest Advances & Controversies, San Juan, PR, 10/18-20/96 (Victor A. Marcial, MD), 10/18/1996 - 10/20/1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - PMA Board of Trustees Meeting 10/17/96, 10/17/1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lehigh University, 10/13/96, Bethlehem, PA--Myer Alperin's Honorary Degree, 10/13/1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - ACR Annual Mtg., Regretted, 9/29-10/2/96 (commences 9/27), San Antonio Marriott Rivercenter, San Antonio, TX, 09/29/1996 - 10/02/1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Assoc. of Community Ca Ctrs. Mtg., 9/21/96, Sheraton Palace Hotel, San Francisco, CA (Dale Fuller, MD), 09/21/1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - PBS Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., Camp Hill, PA - 9/18/96, 09/18/1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cancer of the Bladder Mtg., 9/12-14/96, Leuven, Belgium, 09/12/1996 - 09/14/1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Daytona Beach, FL, 8/29/96, 08/29/1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Santa Fe, NM - 7/27/96 to 8/10/96, 07/27/1996 - 08/10/1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Santa Fe, NM -- BCRI, Summer 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Univ. of Colorado, Denver, CO, 7/26/96 (Howard Wong, MD) Canceled 7/5/96, 07/26/1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - RTOG Semi-Annual Meeting, 7/18-21/96, Philadephia Marriott, 07/18/1996 - 07/21/1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - CARROS Mtg., LaFonda Hotel, Santa Fe, NM, 7/13-14/96 (Dr. J. Lipsett), 07/13/1996 - 07/14/1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Daytona Beach, FL -- 7/3-7/96, 07/03/1996 - 07/07/1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Springer Editorial Bd. Mtg., Heidelberg, Germany, 6/21/96, 06/21/1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - IAMA Board Mtg., 6/15/96 HU Board Rm., 19th Floor NCB, 06/15/1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - LWB Professorship, 6/12/96, Rittenhouse Hotel, 06/12/1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - PBS Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 6/12/96, Camp Hill, PA, regretted, 06/12/1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - ABR Oral Examinations, Louisville, KY, 6/9-12/96, 06/09/1996 - 06/12/1996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Japanese Design Show, 5/23-6/1/96, Osaka, Japan, 05/23/1996 - 06/01/1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - University of MN Review Course, 5/22-24/96, Minneapolis, MN, 05/22/1996 - 05/24/1996 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Saturday 5/18/96 Drinks/Dinner, 05/18/1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Grand Rounds - Presbyterian Med. Ctr. Dept. of Medicinem Philadelphia, PA, 5/10/96, 8-9 am (Dr. Huang), 05/10/1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Radiotherapy of Ocular Disease, 1st Intn't Symposium on Special Aspects of Radiotherapy- 5/4-5/96, Berlin, Germany,Universitatsklinikum Benj. Franklin, 05/04/1996 - 05/05/1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Association of Cancer Executives Mtg., 4/27/96, Society Hill Sheraton, Phila, PA, 04/26/1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - NOMOS-Mtg./Luncheon, 4/26/96, 12:30 pm, (Bernadette Evanovich/Dr. Carol, President), 04/26/1996 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Colgate University--The President's Club Dinner, The Waldorf-Astoria, 4/23/96, 6 p.m., 04/23/1996 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Gilbert H. Fletcher Society Mtg., 4/18-20/96, Williamsburg, VA, 04/18/1996 - 04/20/1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - New York Methodist Hospital, Brooklyn, NY (Mounzer Tchelebi, MD), 4/17/96, 12 noon, 04/17/1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - 5th Annual Dosimetry/Physics Symposium, 3/28-31/96, Hotel Atop the Bellevue,Philadelphia, PA (Mona Weller), 03/28/1996 - 03/31/1996 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - IAMA Board Mtg., New York, NY, Columbia, 3/23/96, 03/23/1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY, 3/16-17/96, 03/16/1996 - 03/17/1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - New York Medical College-Valhalla, NY (Anca Tchelebi, MD), 3/15/96, 03/15/1996 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - PBS Medical Affairs, Camp Hill, PA, Board Room, 3/6/96, 03/06/1996 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Oncovail 1996, Vail, CO, 3/3-8/96, (Philip Rubin, MD), regretted, 03/03/1996 - 03/08/1996 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Cancer Editorial Advisory Bd. Mtg., Atlanta, GA, 2/20/96, (Robert V.P. Hutter, MD), 02/20/1996 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Valere Althouse's 70th Birthday, 2/17/96, Dallas, TX, 02/17/1996 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- UP0019 (Box 19)
  - Society of Gynecologic Oncologists, 2/19-22/95, San Francisco Marriott, CA, 02/19/1995 - 02/22/1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Radiation Therapy Oncology Group Semi-Annual Mtg., San Francisco, CA, 2/16-19/95, 02/16/1995 - 02/19/1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Award Trustees Mtg., 2/2/95, PNC Bank, 2nd Floor, 02/02/1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary Concert and Ball, 1/28/95, Academy of Music, Phila., PA, 01/28/1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia Award Trustees Mtg., 1/24/95, PNC Bank, 2nd Floor, 01/24/1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - WWDB Radio - 7:30 pm (show at 8-9 pm) Bala Cynwyd, PA--hosted by Joel Posner, M.D.--Topic: Cancer, 1/18/95, 01/18/1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Award Trustees Mtg., 1/6/95, 12:15 pm, PNB 2nd Fl. Dining, Land Title Bldg., Broad & Chestnut Sts., 01/06/1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - ACS Med. Affairs Advisory Grp. on Clinical Awards Mtg., 1/12-13/95, Atlanta, GA (Virginia Krawiec), 01/12/1995 - 01/12/1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dinner for Colgate Trustees & Members of James B. Colgate Society, 1/10/95, 6:30 pm, Waldorf-Astoria, NYC, 01/10/1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Daytona Beach, FL, 12/28/94-1/2/95, 12/28/1994 - 01/02/1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Healthcare, 12/8/94, Blue Bell, PA (Lawrence Solin, M.D.), 12/08/1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - RSNA, McCormick Place, Chicago, IL, 11/27-12/2/94, 11/27/1994 - 12/02/1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - American Radium Society-Scientific Program Committee Mtg., 12/14/94, 8 am-Noon, Sheraon Society Hill, Phl, 12/14/1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Portrait Ceremony honoring Dr. Carl Mansfield, 10/24/94, 4 pm, TJU, McClellan Hall, 10/24/1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - ASTRO Meeting, 10/3-6/94, Moscone Center, San Francisco, CA, 10/03/1994 - 10/06/1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - PBS Medical Affairs Committee Mtg., 9/28/94, Camp Hill, PA, 09/28/1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Healthcare, 9/12/94, Blue Bell, PA (Lawrence Solin, M.D.), 09/12/1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - ACR Annual Mtg., New Orleans, LA, 9/17-21/94, 09/17/1994 - 09/21/1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - IAMA Fall Board Mtg., Sat., 9/17/94, College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 09/17/1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Daytona Beach, FL 8/31-9/5/94, 08/31/1994 - 09/05/1994 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - IAMA Board Mtg. - 8/20/94, New York City, NY, 08/20/1994 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Santa Fe, NM -- 7/30-8/13/94, 07/30/1994 - 08/13/1994 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 7/12-17/94, London, England, 7/17-23/94, Helsinki, Finland--Univ. of Turku; Savonlinna Opera Festival, 07/12/1994 - 07/23/1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - IAMA Board Mtg. - 6/25/94, 10-4 pm, College of Physicians (Richard Lippin, MD), 06/25/1994 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Brain Tumor Symposium, Wistar Inst., 6/24/94, 1-6 p.m., 06/24/1994 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Norristown Regional Cancer Center, "Advances in Oncology 1994", 6/8/94, Plymouth Mtg., PA., 06/08/1994 (Box 19, Folder 26)